morning's Kobe's good morning it's my
room now moved check it out
brah
what's up my new room my bed on the
floor back there thank you now I plant I
love my plant
happy Sunday happy Mother's Day
everybody honor your mother and father
its commandant y'all should do it
check out my my Mondrian my
ex-girlfriend painted this for me it's
kind of nice we haven't sold the Ford
Fusion yet we're gonna go trade it in
for a Honda Accord thank you thank you
so my map record II I'm no longer a
logan paul fan but I do think the merch
looks good
where is my family back in New Jersey
bros know we only hire engineers comma
only hires engineers because it's
engineers that move the world forward
that's not sure we hire a few other
people but it's mostly engineers
um yeah Honda Accord steers down to zero
okay so I'll tell you guys what we're
talking about today welcome welcome
welcome thank you I like the pink - all
right so you guys have all seen this
room guys have all seen it
we're hiring two positions we're hiring
a bunch of positions ml guy is still
around he's doing pretty well pretty
happy with the new ml guy but what I'm
really here to show off is this room
here this room is gonna be full of
engineers guys we're hiring okay all
right all right all right so let's go to
the board downstairs and it's confession
time about to tell you all something you
have my old bedroom now to fill with
engineers okay guys so I haven't told
anyone this yet but we're gonna tell you
right here on periscope
uh a couple weeks ago we raised five
million dollars so we have we have five
million dollars and we raised it at a
100 billion dollar valuation so yeah
here's a thing right
I'm not big on you know it's not an
accomplishment right it's really not an
accomplishment to raise money if you
think it's wouldn't raise 100 or raise
50 million but I valuation is a hundred
it's an accomplishment to raise money
what you're really doing is you're
you're you're selling off your company
but yeah so you like the diagram I will
get a better marker for the rest of the
stuff I have tried okay so guys the key
word from here on out is focus we know
exactly what we're building not ready to
tell y'all yet we know exactly what it
is we're building it's gonna take about
18 months and by the end of it I hope
that we're going to be worth 1 billion
dollars because if you're starting a
start-up your goal is to be unicorn 1
billion dollars
I was checking list of unicorns there's
not that many of them we're not building
a bullet train no you guys could
probably guess we're doing but yes we're
trying to 10x this hundred million we're
trying to turn a crack rock into a
mountain yeah that's the plan guys 1
billion dollars we are hiring so if
you're good if you know people who are
good we're looking for you we have
something incredible to bring to the
world guys you look at the EON you look
at the Panda
you think you think I did this to build
yawns Amanda's bro I did this to build
revolutionary that changes the
world and that's what we're here to do
so we're hiring we're hiring engineers
and more engineers and other engineers
yeah I know I know we're at the hype
it's not hype guys it's not hype if it's
real I'm not promising you this
is real like this is actually I gave a
realistic timeline a realistic plan yo I
did some CEO on Friday
I calculated like evidence and
annualized recurring revenues and did
market research and this is
actually achievable if you're coming
here thinking that you're gonna make a
huge salary this is not the company for
you it's a Jimmy world quote do you want
the work more than the reward you come
here if you want to change the world
ah if you're looking to make 300 K check
out the Toyota Research Institute I hear
they pay really well okay um so that's
that but yeah focus 18 months 1 billion
dollars um
no better than Google no we're not we're
not better than Google but that's okay
Wayne was valued at about 70 billion
dollars Cruz is probably valued at about
10 so 1 billion is is small in
self-driving car game I mean even am I
good at math I'm pretty good at math I
ain't got perfect scores on my math SATs
but yeah so we raised we raised we
raised five million a hundred million
dollar valuation don't raise a lot of
money don't sell a lot of your company
never ever give up a board seat because
you don't want to get khalaq nicked you
want a Zuckerberg I'm absolutely we
offer out we offer options to people who
work here
um if you work here if you join now and
we succeed you probably make ten million
dollars
if we succeed and you join right now
your your stuff will probably in four
years out of even with ten dollars if we
succeed and that's the game yo you know
what I've been reading guys the will to
power this is super relevant today
do we have a pool um no no it's not ten
million in eighteen months yes it ground
for four years and we really got a we
really got to ride out the tail but
that's the main thing I'm here to talk
about what am i drinking right now I got
a I got a venti iced coffee from
Starbucks really we're going hard today
get things to do but yeah so a few
things to show off to you guys
vesting schedule you know this is a for
you four years one year cliff the
standard what am I gonna show you guys
today I could show you our latest
training machine so our new models use
reinforcement learning and in order to
do reinforcement learning you need big
computers so I got this guy right here
that's my latest and greatest 10 GPUs
one box
we've got some more 3d printers the Army
is the Army's not printing right now no
these are falling off
[Music]
nvidia ten nvidia gpus all these people
down here I'm moving upstairs old guys
wanna know what's in these boxes
yeah boxes browse there's a oneplus of a
TP you know how many transistors a lot
but yeah guys so this is scope II Sunday
we're not here to to to to on
people today that's not what this Co P
Sunday's about we don't sleep we go hard
welcome to comedy I we're getting a
Honda Accord but that is really what I'm
here to talk about today your bike just
Andrew focus 18 months 1 billion
dollars get we're mapping you guys know
we're mapping you saw the mapping scope
ease the mapping is starting to work
Harold bro Harold slam it's the future
we have our own slam system it's quite
good but that's really all I'm here to
talk about today we're hiring give me a
job at comma a I get an early get rich
get in late get yeah that sounds
right I'm tiring a PID guy if you know
things about controls will hire you do I
work on ml today I'm working on that
well today yeah no we're a little - now
you know why because this isn't here's
the thing about hype right here's the
thing about everything don't be a
hypocrite so many people in lives are
hypocrites they say that they know
is not true to like build something guys
if I didn't believe what I wrote on the
board there I wouldn't write it why am I
here what am i doing I'm rich I have a
great life but we're sure to win
self-driving cars and that's exactly
what we're gonna do
why am i a Python guy I'm code in C++
kind of I know a little super sports my
codes evil flows pretty well ml is going
off ml is going well new models new
calibration oh-oh that's the other thing
I want to show you guys yes we of course
building artificial intelligence eons
are about to get some serious
stability improvements we've had a
full-time engineer working for four
weeks on Eon stability we haven't
shipped any of these improvements yet
and what we have here is the Eon testing
closet what guys rich for a while now
this is the Eon testing closet and we've
had eons now run for a hundred hours 100
hours straight driving a car so we don't
want Young's to crash anymore and we're
working hard on stability on system
stability oh I can show you what I can
show you at the front end of that looks
like we'll go to we'll go to testing
calm in our life bro common needs car
hackers yeah if you're a car hacker I
will hire you okay really just here's
what we hired based on we hire based on
two things intelligence and motivation
intelligence kind of in an IQ sense and
then you're not allowed to talk about IQ
anymore but we do we don't IQ test you
but you got to be smart you know you got
it you got to be intelligence and you
got to be motivated and you got to be
motivated right like you know if you're
asking like well I could good 400k
Toyota great bro go work at Toyota if
you want to change the world maybe do it
all right so we could see up here ya'll
watching Death Note pretty good
every more power it's pretty good
programmers need focus um yeah yeah City
why and gonna like those nagging high
schools Stuyvesant Burke County
academies college doesn't matter causes
a scam there's great new podcast out a
16z with this guy is like education is
all about signaling in this crap huge
waste of money you guys want to learn
stuff you have the greatest tool in the
history of the world to learn stop what
is that greatest tool in the history of
the world you can learn anything you
want
wouldn't sell afford time training for a
court next week training for Honda
Accord Google yeah we have the Internet
the internet it's it's the Internet has
changed my life guys but yeah so this is
testing open pilot CPU usage RAM usage
how long it's been running for now it
looks like it's down I will have to look
into that but yeah cleaning up all the
memory leaks for cleaning up all the
crashes stability but we really got to
come back to if we focus for 18 months
will be worth 1 billion dollars by the
Internet's change my life guys I'd be no
one without the internet got a credit
bro you got a credit Oh guys I college
college like you're the Roman fire
brigade the Roman fire brigade were
people who basically used to come around
and they'd be like oh I see your houses
on fire
maybe you should go pay us some money
and we'll put that out if you didn't pay
that go to your neighbors be like a fire
spread real fast you know maybe you
should not pay up those guys those guys
is a scam our current valuation is 105
million dollars so that's an some new
dropping right here for you guys on
periscope I was rejected from MIT
I own the domain I hate MIT calm yeah
how is not very good student in high
school you know cuz I'm dumb that's what
my husband my teachers would tell me
that's my gay teachers I love high
school but I did do really badly in high
school say what do what oh I can scroll
up and see common uh I went I went to
Carnegie Mellon briefly I took some
great classes I learned some great
things but few very talented professors
it's all about finding like the few
professors who actually want to teach
you things
here's the thing the systems in place in
the world today do not incentivize value
creation
they do not incentivize actually
teaching you anything
but there's some people who like against
all the odds just have this intrinsic
desire to create in this intrinsic
desire to teach other people how to
create and that's who you got to find
now none of these systems are worth
what I think about coding dojo I don't
really like those bootcamp things
motivate yourself I'm telling you what
I'm doing today
yo this is paper really psyched about D
correlated batch normalization so I'm
gonna try to implement this intensive
flow and we'll see what goes so if you
guys know what Bachelor realization is
uh D correlated batch normalization
there's a projective transform on the
vector space 2d correlate the things
right because if you're if you're things
in your neural net are correlated you're
wasting capacity but if you can D
correlate them you get capacity back so
it's really exciting and you could do it
you can do it you see like you can't D
correlate in a nonlinear way but you can
if you're talking straight-up
correlation in a linear way you can
actually do that transformation um
who'd have thought that linear algebra
was gonna be the science that was gonna
change the that was gonna determine our
future linear algebra and a little bit
of calculus heõs to know much calculus
it was perfect it's this perfect like
the things that I was good at happened
to be the things that were like good and
like multivariable calculus not so good
looking house it was cool no no we
didn't hack before it firmware I'm given
the Ford back I'm over for it's not the
year of the for it anymore part of our
focus alright guys let me tell you
there's really six cars that we're
focused on if you have one of these six
cars you're in luck
if you don't have one of these six cars
you're out of luck we have the CRV the
Civic and the Accord in the Honda
Department and in the Toyota department
we have the rav4 the Camry and the
Corolla
right rola there we go um these six
these six cars of the future if you have
one of these six you're in luck
what's the cheapest I don't know
couldn't tell you I'm rich what Oh God
because everybody's using that stupid
data speed Oh super cruise Cabana little
seem able I don't know um Andy's
out driving our Cadillac right now he's
gonna move to that upstairs upstairs
pretty nice alright let's go chill up in
that room for a little bit um is Eddy
paper rich yet you'll have to ask daddy
that I don't know man
we're kind of got it on crypto early to
everyone around the office so we got out
hopefully not everyone got out I got it
I'm now over crypto no I'm kidding
always keep your portfolio balance when
crypto appreciates you're gonna keep the
same percentage it don't good investment
advice I also bought Tesla stock yo I
bought Tesla stock when Ilan like
flipped off the people during the
conference call I was like that is such
a boss move um that I bought Tesla stock
and it's up 10%
what a deal no minivan no we support the
Civic the Accord the CRV and we support
the Corolla the Camry and the rav4 and
that's it
if we hypothetically start releasing a
cup of Reef lashes they're gonna be for
those six cars or no others you on musk
work
I don't think I think he lawns got
better things going on the work I come I
mean commas lit but like I SpaceX is
cooler like it's just cooler than in
like a but that said if you go work its
basis you're gonna make way less of an
impact because it's a much bigger
company SpaceX is a is a six thousand
person company now and we are 15 we're
hiring we hope to be twenty by the end
of the year so we're hiring five people
this year
yeah crossovers code like let's see are
bees those rappers rap for is the third
best-selling car for a bit oh yo check
this out balcony for our newest software
engineers come out hang out on the
beautiful balcony where is viv it's
Sunday guys only I'm at the office on
Sun there's no a few other people here
but viv is probably home talk about life
what do you want to know vape wild out
there not smoking weed yesterday I don't
think we smoked weed today that was that
was my yesterday
smoking weed cleaning this room hood up
clerical work sorry
when did I wake up today thirty the cord
sport if it's the same stuff yeah come
on drugs I did drink that big coffee
today though that is that is real I did
drink have that big coffee yesterday
smoke weed maybe once every once a
weekend Bros Willow gang no I'm over the
little gang I don't know I haven't
watched logo ball got bad after he came
back because he tried to be like
politically correct and like appease
audiences Oh week never apologize bros
don't get collect nicked you know didn't
apologize Zuckerberg cuz you got a
sucker burger that's right we use Azure
because they gave us more free money
never give up never surrender absolutely
yeah sucker
thoughts are on tensorflow vs. pi torch
I use tensorflow
no real reason it kind of came out first
ego votes pretty nice now - so you got
like that same PI torch niceness yeah of
course of course new products yeah but
it's gonna take a bit it's gonna take
eighteen months um how much for a verse
yo I will do a verse if you have a
following and you actually want me on
your rap track I will absolutely write
you some 16 bars reach out to me on
Soundcloud sify.com slash Tom Cruise -
two zeros what positions
okay so we're hiring for driver
monitoring so you got to do like ml and
data science we're hiring for firmware
Panta firmer hypothetical firmware and
bring up for future of hardware products
that may or may not exist know things
about barbarian like see and drivers and
stuff we're hiring for mapping there's a
Roch Roch Roch bro nice that would be
funny those that actually haven't done a
periscope
when will young be replaced he also be
supported certainly through the rest of
the year guys were a foam company we're
gonna release new hardware every year
what do you want to do with 10 meters 10
centimeters bro we're hiring two people
for mapping we're hiring a full stack
engineer and we're hiring like a data
scientist pretty much those four if you
know things about ml data science code
and Python low level stuff drivers see
that's all good if you know things about
controls vehicle dynamics so always hire
people like that really you come in here
I'll tell you what our interview process
is I ask you questions and I kind of
probe your knowledge you do the same
thing to me pro bono but then like if by
the end of the interview we're having a
conversation where we're both teaching
each other things are really if you're
just teaching me things if you're way
smarter than me
absolutely hired here if you're teaching
me things by the end of the interview
we're having like legit conversation
that's what it is like that's what it
that's what it takes to get hired around
here know things this is I see the same
thing on games to like know things I
don't care even really what you know
things of that but like know things you
know so if people just don't know things
seeing C++ developer looking for a job
give me a job I comment on AI we got a
phone screen set up what's the speed of
light bro do you know life is work what
else is there to do Jordan Peterson is
this great thing he's like look man you
gotta believe you got to believe it you
gotta believe in an evil
you gotta believe that some things are
bad because if nothing is bad that
nothing is good and it looks good what
do we wake up and what are we what are
we work toward all day know if you teach
me things about history during an m/l
and ever you know you don't get the job
but I would love it like I went on a
date and some girl taught me things
about history that would be great there
you go Greg you know this beetle light
but the problem is everyone can google
it right now you do that in person too
that fast
do I believe in God Lee I mean maybe not
the judeo-christian god but like
somebody created the world right rice
what about ask what the implications of
the speed of light are I mean that's
faster than anything yeah you can get
into it's communicating fashion the
speed of light possible what if I use
quantum entanglement bro we didn't talk
Iran people say this I honestly someone
else probably did it we do nothing with
Iran we just just does not we live in
virtual reality
yeah probably something like that aliens
created us yeah I mean something created
us and that's what I called God right I
need some philosophical teaching what
the reading reaching bro I didn't get it
much when I was younger like I read
Nietzsche when I was like
and it was confusing to me I didn't like
to understand and then I read an R and
when I was young and I understood it's
very easy and then you grow up with that
and you're like okay let me find a
slightly more nuanced philosophy here
yeah yeah oh god Randy they're good
books they really are good books if you
guys haven't read like Atlas Shrugged
and Fountainhead like they're very
enjoyable to read as a lifestyle
philosophy you know it's fiction
come on but it's enjoyable like it's a
good book God is everything yes God's
nature job's collective as a user and
fan yeah do I believe why does Torvalds
do I believe he exists it as a person
yes very easy to understand
misunderstands objective is I mean it's
objective I don't actually think is a
way to like live life but it certainly
has good core points you probably have
with coding is you hate the theory you
don't need that much theory yes that is
Torvalds once at a conference I think
he's I think he's incredible I think the
best song for engineers in the world the
fact that he still does like the merging
in of the pull requests to the kernel
the Linux kernel is much higher quality
code than the windows I've read the
Windows kernel code I've read the Mac OS
kernel code oh man well there's kernel
is way better if God is good and
powerful who said anything about God
being good that sounds like some
Christian stuff I told you I believe in
God I just believe God is powerful I'm
hope I'm good I think good is a human
invention have I addressed the great key
I don't know what that is do I know
about kernel what do you want to know
yeah I know
Colonel I know what exists do you want
to know have I addressed the gray key
what is gray key
what's my IQ and I could talk about that
I don't care cracks iPhones anymore I
have an iPhone don't have my iPhone
I'm sure I'm sure it works I'm sure
someone's making money off of it stop
light stop and go a new model oh yeah
yeah always coming soon no they'll be
out by the end of here the new model is
coming sooner models are working can i
hack Google again what do you mean by
that
I probably could hack Google I probably
couldn't hack Google and get away with
it and that's a lot harder and again
like yeah what do you mean by hack right
could I get access to people's data yeah
probably so the real thing is you don't
go after Google why not just go after
the person directly can I change the
front page of Google com
yep probably it would probably take like
a year new calibration is gonna be sick
new generations so fast um new
calibration is is fast yeah when we map
the rest of the world that's not America
I don't know man
after the GE PR I'm very bearish on
Europe
I'm very bearish I'm like touching any
European stuff yeah talk to you talk to
your representatives tell them that laws
like that are crap how many hours do I
work every day how many hours of my
awake life is work how interactive I am
thank you I'm like a cam girl except
nobody pays me
that's about Google Group like this is
sick demo women is work is Google or the
NSA more secure probably the NSA only
because they have less outward-facing
services right Google has a lot of
points that you could attack ever
alright bro you're bad that's that's
just vulgar what do you think we can do
about the roads in California you almost
can't see the lanes but you can and
people don't crash so I'm sure machines
got into not hacking Iran I don't care I
like the counter alright except nobody
pays me I hated the Google president no
no but you have to make the computer say
on because people do like it sounded
good and what that's really going to I'm
absolutely not a white supremacist you
guys but why have the computer say oh
because really what it is is all right
you're you're asking me if I can hack
you're banned the white supremacist
guys ban we don't need that talk here
guilfoyle doesn't like the arm I don't
even know what you mean by that sativa
duplex beating time-tested it kind of is
in a way well what that's really going
to do what Google duplex is going to do
is make humans a very expensive endpoint
so it's gonna make it very expensive for
humans to you know if you're a
restaurant you don't have an online
booking system you're gonna get calls
from computers and I know who Gilfoyle I
got like guilfoyle the actor Gilfoyle on
Silicon Valley like gig that's I'm
talking about like what level of the
meta this is on yeah like something
called ensalada this is great there's
gonna um you're both gonna have a
legitimate conversation but there has to
be a reason that exists right no no
evolutionary algorithms let's start with
Zuck we got to talk about weather sucks
human before we get to me we don't use
evolutionary algorithms because they're
not as powerful as
search like they're not as powerful as
convex optimization right if you think
about what gave rise to humans maybe
evolution design the architecture but
the learning the real power comes from
economics optimization I love machine
learning algorithms then the search is
just way less powerful you can show that
convex optimization is just more
powerful there's a guy on periscope that
hates the Zuckerberg because that breaks
over what are some of the problems
people will be working on so winning
self-driving cars I mean that's that's
the whole problem right like how do you
win self-driving cars so you'll be
working on things like things like map
and things like machine learning you
know how do you so we have maps right we
gotta put them all on a big map we got
to do we got to put that in a database
so we can quickly access it when I
upload my brain on a computer okay I got
to be a little bit careful with that
what do I think about Bill Gates or
Steve Jobs something like Bill Gates
versus Steve Jobs I mean they both have
things going for them it's hard to get
real information still about Steve Jobs
because he's kind of a deified after his
death so throwing planes not to be
honest actually to be honest if you're
talking about cities these like small
hop drones are pretty good however I
don't do machine learning read the
Internet
hey breakthroughs in depth detection
we're working on pretty good to punch
supervised stuffs getting good mask this
off store locally now will stream them
over the internet with database to be
used my sequel are you using acid or
base databases we use my sequel
do you believe set a V job I don't even
know what that is my safe is pretty good
like it's just like what else are you
really gonna do come on go bro I'm gonna
go with that no sequel slow
he's my sequel on the back end what does
comma hardware look like an 18 months
well you'll say just a cramp
it's I'll tell you I'll here's the end
here's the hint I'll give you it's gonna
have more cameras 360 each base cuz I'm
one of the Apache things I should know
this stuff better way case
do you work with no sequel big data
stuffs um so a lot of art like big big
stuff is stored as flat files no so we
don't like put them videos in my cygwin
stuff that's all done as flat files 360
[Music]
but no I mean it's gonna be like if
anything comes out with a 360 down it's
gonna be a lot more expensive and it's
not gonna be much more at first we gotta
get there everyone will go yeah cloud is
a great idea right everyone should go to
the cloud except for like GPUs now
unfortunately there's still really
expensive in the cloud so it's worth it
to have my premise but if you're talking
about just compute and keeping servers
off and reliability and stuff like that
you want to go cloud maybe stereo say
what I think about quantum computing I
think it's mostly a scam yeah even the
other side is actually this is a a
quantum computing probably mostly a scam
I believe that P equals B Q P if you
want to get real in depth about this I
don't think there's any problems that
quantum computers can solve faster than
classical computers I do think there's a
classical time factoring algorithm I
think will find it like ten years of
privacy guys get over it get over
privacy if you're interested in privacy
you just you gonna lose you build a
recommender system why
seems like all manufactures gonna come a
self-driving future yeah just like all
phones come with smartphone feature
except they run Android right all phones
are gonna come with internet browser
well yeah and like some of the
manufacturers tried to make their own
phone with internet browser and we know
exactly how that ended up miss your
Nokia n900 bro
yeah don't use the Internet if you think
about privacy that's absolutely right
you want privacy go live in a cabin and
honestly people still find your I
absolutely love my work
yeah convert to pickle in a Berlin
computer we're gonna do partnerships I
vomit when I hear that word yeah it's
disgusting our manufacturer is going to
be allowed to use our open-source
software on their cars absolutely
sidekick to best phone made by Andy
Rubin
surveillance state yeah I mean the only
problem is that we're not surveilling
the surveillance day all right
distribution yeah you can sure what do
you mean you could communicate securely
that's not like a problem right like
like like you're misunderstanding what
partnerships aren't really a bad
question they just kind of disgust me a
little bit no I'm not gay
kind of cool to be gay I think that
partnerships are a new band question no
what was the thing before
oh about key distribution no I mean like
that's not likely the NSA can't crack
your photography yes do I know about
Stallman yes he exists but the problem
has a lot more to do with the analog
code right like any and it's not the
it's not the like communication that
they can intercept it's like well why
don't they just hijack your phone or why
don't they just like send a guy to tell
you or there's much cheaper ways to to
violate your privacy than cracking your
409 six bit RSA right like don't don't
privacy's a scam guys security is a huge
scam I went to RSA this year I could not
believe the entire floor is just filled
with scammers trying to sell you their
box I don't know I mean I think if
you're gay you're into that right
physical access is way easier yeah
license plate readers are everywhere
yeah yeah cameras are everywhere man you
want to know about the license plate
reader Network so for them we
process all the license plates what's my
favorite engineer like people I don't
know how many people guys yeah if it
digital secured I mean it's not a West
role tonight I don't know I don't really
watch the season yet I've heard mediocre
things I probably I should I should
catch out I've been watching definitely
what do I think of Andrew McAfee you'd
be like the guy who killed his neighbor
and beliefs of bath salts you know a I
can write own code well sort of that's
what I kind of is localized shadows in
the road of sunset yeah HDR is a real
solution too
that was just having up to Namak range
of the cameras we've shipped HDR a
future cuck streaming live rod pink
hoodie yay you know I brought your bad
no I don't know I got it nope oh that's
my favorite noise together application
the hunter prize the hunter price the
hunter prize is sweet make the smallest
self-extracting archives Kenna for Cappy
dia I think the winning entry might have
analyst um no there's a guy Byron all
working as open source thing called sea
mix it's really cool
we should worldwide alright bro
man thank you for commenting again I
love banning people feels great we
expect to light it up for Tesla anytime
soon no I'm kissing Tesla look so he's
one of my losers Tesla's were quite
awesome people I want to beat them
legitimately in a here's the thing like
I don't think he'll on busca actually
likes me I like him I'm a big fan right
that he looks at me like some like you
know to ban before why I banned everyone
cause it's banding right Sunday sorry
what function is working best with
backpropagation I like Adam Adams pretty
good Tesla isn't so hot
you gotta get to use debt man Prius is
absolutely still supported what I saw my
entire company Tesla maybe I don't know
I don't know if musk aids me good chef
on Twitter I love that he does that man
was the CEO gee I'm doing that I don't
think you are Mosca's jealous of my
talent
I think he's smarter than me right now
maybe I'll be doing in a few years I'm
light enough was good I know yeah I mean
no there's no such thing as a perfect
self-driving cars just like superhuman
self-driving cars I mean maybe there is
right but it's like you don't need a
perfect chess player go player to build
something that's far superhuman
I don't go to DEFCON anymore I wanted to
speak there last year and they said no
I sort of don't like what Def Con has
become um so I don't go anymore
nope I don't want to be famous and I'm
not that much I don't care
it's money is worthless to me how'd it
become smarter bad news I don't really
think it's possible I think IQ is pretty
fixed throughout your life and you can
become dumber but I know if he could
become smarter thoughts on TP use ah not
a fan I think Def Con has because it's
run by it's run by like the perpetual
conference crowd I'm like all these
conferences are kind of becoming
homogenized by the kind of people who go
to conferences you have a merger of like
like industry and maybe some like like
social justice warrior ask themes you
know you see the people with like pink
hair or the organizers of the conference
is like like that's cool if you want to
have a conference about that but like
it's becoming everything I heard good
things still about CCC I heard good
things still about CCC I don't give a
I don't want any famous bro I don't
want to be like super rich I just want I
want to know everything you can train
your brain to become smarter yeah I mean
you know you can just become stupid or I
kind of think about these I don't know
that maybe it's okay but DEFCON DEFCON
this you can definitely do things to
increase productivity and maximize
ridiculous yeah that's my job am i doing
any CTS not a place if you have said
anymore all right guys
maybe we'll do it we'll do three more
minutes make it 45 minutes I can't wait
till some journalist like goes through
this it is like the problematic things
about common eyes periscopes thanks for
the attention bro can you win at DEFCON
I did a few years could I went solo
there's probably one year I had a chance
I do drink coffee
wisdoms not fixed yeah juicy GFS they're
pretty cool did I see Avengers and
advocacy the superhero movies there look
beautifies about the superhero movies
they're taking up room where there could
be good new movies it's the same story
repackaged every single time could I
wouldn't Def Con right now I'm not a
poet to practice for a year Reed Scott
Alexander stuff about growth mindset
it's it's a nice fiction but I'm not
really sure it's true can you buy the
Ford giraffe I think we'll open source
it coffee's only a carcinogen in
California good thing I'm not as away
now I'm in California I had a code
faster make a plan musk aids me yeah I
fell it does know San Francisco Ida Pro
is good because sleeping the ones me
anything better what deep learning
papers do you recommend to read um I'm
excited about D Carly Bachelor ization
that's what we're to do right now life
as a carcinogen that sounds about right
oh don't be so worried about how you're
gonna die just be worried about how
you're gonna live forever map Europe not
only America and Canada maybe Mexico -
we like Mexico I'm with the Mexicans
pretty nice but I went to I went to like
they played pile-on Carmen and stuff a
buffer overflows I think we kind of
passed by froze I sold over the wire
void things like that do this show like
she's hard I don't really talk about
security much anymore
it's kind of boring did we sell the for
no not yeah next week can use her map
Europe yeah will do God won't consider
European I don't know what's good the
America Maps working first cost of
living in San Francisco is insane yeah
man Peter teal complaints it's like I
give money to these companies and then
they paid it employs maybe the employees
panel landlords I'm really just helping
these new be landlords out I was that
name were he growth mindset Scott
Alexander he writes this blog called
Slate star codex it's really good check
it out West Hollywood hoodie we get
already do our merch that's what I was
telling to them yesterday I'm like I
want to get some mercis like nice what
am i doing today I'm reading some more
in EJ and I'm gonna implement that paper
why am i happy all the time because
courage do we keep always sad
five is great we live in paradise I went
out for breakfast this morning I love
going out for breakfast I'm like
sometimes I got a deal with stuff and
I'm not happy but today I don't have
much to deal with I'm hanging out it's a
good day come a pocket key I don't know
what that is men hackers are sad I'm not
sad favorite breakfast food oh I mean I
love waffles but I don't feel good after
I eat waffles you know life is great has
nothing to do it
I honestly think if you have a mentality
that life is great you end up just like
getting money and if you have a
mentality but life is you like
don't I love pizza I've been eating a
lot more McDonald's lately too Donnell
sex pretty good be careful where you eat
don't eat more than 2,000 calories a day
they'll be fat you need a comma hoodie
do have any furniture in here we're
gonna put some desks up in here
oh my dolls kind of nasty that's kind of
true don't you one 2,000 calories daiva
be sure to think it matters what you eat
as long as you eat I think all of like
nutrition is a scam as long as you eat
2,000 calories or less pretty that's it
no I was never fat bro am I gonna jazz
up the place you're at right now we're
gonna throw some desks up in here do I
care about my body I care about nothing
fat but beyond that what if you're
Michael Phelps oh you see me in a pool
okay Michael Phelps this is maverick
courage it is about a perch I kind of
like it I'm over Logan Paul no I think
nutrition is mostly a scam like I think
that they change what's the new hip
nutrition every once in a while where's
my girlfriend Vegas with this girl two
weekends ago that was pretty cool
last weekend that's pretty funny what
made me get a Roomba
I bought it I'm very disappointed with
it actually it's kind of crap it cost
way too much money do I exercise not
like really focus sometimes I walk
we just don't know yeah like I don't
know maybe there's some answers to
nutrition but
I think I think they just don't know do
I exercise I can do something I could do
some push-ups having a girlfriend is
cool if that's that that's a personal
decision then money has influenced you
know absolutely like they like put out
some like new scam like don't eat carbs
or like gotta eat like don't eat gluten
or you know you got to eat kale kale
also superfood I think I do a backflip
on a trampoline yeah oh I'm sorry you
don't like how I look your thanks bro
really help it out by my self-esteem
here drop money influences all research
unfortunately am I gonna announce
speaking next time who's my first
girlfriend other song I'm not gonna say
her name who was they who's they what do
you mean did I say they they the great
conspiracy and he upgrades for the
adhesive I don't know girls I don't
think I'm woody get gets a test because
he wanted was a girlfriend he did he had
this interview where he came out he's
like look man I would just be so sad if
I like build rockets and like had no one
to come home and share was a really
human moment I kind of liked it where
will I be in 30 years old probably on
this couch talking to you guys no I
don't think about the future that much
like that I think about the future in
like grand broad strokes like it'll
where's like technology going the like
in terms of my future who cares
all right scope he's winning
self-driving cars I hope do I plan to
teach my dad's a teacher I don't think
they'd like me I don't know if
credentials what is common look like in
two years unicorn bro unicorn that's my
new thing
unicorn where is technology going
I mean that's a long and complex
question 18 months Apple turns off the
fancy computer you start Siri that's
pretty cool it's good nice quiet sculpey
what I think her veganism again it's a
personal choice if you choose to be a
vegan good for you if you just stand on
the corner and scream about how non
veganism is immoral but no no no this
periscope I call my one yesterday no
phone call I did I wish to have mother's
day sorry I was watching some more
videos yesterday they're pretty cool all
right I should get back to work too
thank you for joining we are hiring come
work a comma a I ask voice Co covered
cow may I
good Sunday yeah Andrew entering office
really he's really killed his reputation
yo-yo peace out bro